<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy?  The Psalms Make Encouragement Easier</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/30/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/30/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;when-just-wanting-to-say-something-isn-t-enough&#34;&gt;When Just Wanting to Say Something Isn&amp;rsquo;t Enough&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a shy guy, especially if &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; are having a hard time. It may not seem like it, should we meet, but I find interacting with other people stressful and draining, which is another way of saying I am a natural introvert. Conversations are hard – and conversations with suffering people are harder; when I see a person who has needs, who could obviously use a warm word of encouragement, I feel a little frozen to the ground. Unsure what to say, the right words don’t simply materialize in my brain. The more often this happens, the more discouraged I become, wondering, could I ever strengthen others?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever felt this way? Does your heart go out to that friend, mired in a dark season of life or battling trials – only to find when you see them, you have nothing to say? or that when you do speak, what falls out of your mouth falls far short of the good you intended?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picture for a moment the challenge of encouragement could be reduced from art to organization; would that help? Think of an artist painting a beautiful image from a brilliant, imaginative concept in his mind – then picture yourself outdoors on your covered porch, arranging the tables and chairs in proper order; which seems easier? As an introvert I tend think of encouragement as a difficult and mystical art form; but what if it were less like a burst of artistic imagination, and more a (relatively) mundane task of putting some words, like furniture, into the right place? Would we be more likely to actually practice it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine for a moment the challenge of encouragement could be reduced from art to organization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Psalms are full of material ready-made for the purpose of encouragement. They are a natural fit just by their construction, their focus. They tend to lean less on doctrine or on instruction for life, and more on exploring the inner workings of the heart. The language there is illustrative; it sends light into the deep crevices in the human experience with honesty and energy and a tender, faithful grace which we couldn’t hope to duplicate, were we to sit down with pen and paper and spend years trying. The Psalms are, after all, the word of God, despite their source straight from the experiences of a man; they are paradoxical in that sense - an undistorted, mirror-like reflection of our real life, read back to us in reverse as it were, through the glass of God’s truth and grace. In the mystery at work, there is no dilution or minimization of God’s power on the one hand, or of the pain and joy of the human condition, on the other. The Psalms are a compact miracle of clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also the inheritance of every Christian, and we should lay claim on this enormous mineral deposit of material. For believers who want to encourage others, it’s our time to find a pickaxe and shovel, to find a suitable point of ground and start digging. The Psalms are meant for sharing, in good times but particularly in bad; with the glad, but also with souls stuck in the deep and airless recesses of life. There are resources in this book here which bring life and the sunshine of hope to those who have no hope; words which provoke a lifeless faith; phrases that can be broken down like nuggets, packed with rich gold. Hope and faith are here in the context of anxiety, deep depression, panic, adversity, fear, temptation and any trouble. There is no lack in the love of God found here toward you, to match the trouble you might find in your own experience; these words are conceived in the mind of God with care and deep consideration, the same care that formed your physical body “…intricately woven in the depths of the earth, Your eyes saw my unformed substance…” (Ps. 139) These words are personal, they are meant for you, and for this life full of trouble and care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must not give fools’ gold when we could have shared the real thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And they are not meant to be topped, when you share them with others. They are not meant to be replicated or imitated – we must feel no great need to speak ad-lib like a kind of spiritual stand-up comic, “in the spirit of the Bible”, making “the truth our own” as goes the expression. There is a time to just sit and listen, but when the moment comes to speak, we must not give fools’ gold when we could have shared the real thing. Is it real love, to share with our neighbor less than the best? Encouragement means sharing the Word with our hurting brother; we should not redefine it as a misguided effort at creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, rearrange and index Scriptures in your mind; put your creativity to work at the job of placing a finger on just the right bit of a Psalm for your particular friend, the one with that particular &lt;em&gt;thing&lt;/em&gt;. With enough of the Word at your mental fingertips, this job becomes more routine; it becomes attainable – it becomes enjoyable. This is a task of mastery and memorization, not of inspiration; the bit of Scripture you want isn’t really out of reach – duplicating it and its power, is. We were not meant for such a task – God has prepared good works for us to do, and if encouragement is a good work, we must believe that his Word prepares us for that effort. If we will read the Psalms and take them to heart, we will see that it amply supplies us for encouraging others. When we quote them, we will have confidence, as there will never be a question that we are falling short of the truth. That confidence will give rise to a greater interest in serving others, and make us more enthusiastic in pursuit of more material to store up for the task.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If encouragement is a good work, we must believe that his Word prepares us for that effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get the Psalms into your heart, so you can encourage yourself; but double your efforts, if you want to use them to encourage others. Don’t be shy about it. You may find that inhibition will no longer be the obstacle to encouragement it once was; you’ll instead see reason for thankfulness, that you have been given a “word in season”, just in that moment when you most desire to speak it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/23/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/23/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;parents-the-psalms-are-for-adults-too&#34;&gt;Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the story of Jesus in the home of Lazarus, Mary &amp;amp; Martha, we see famous scene where Mary sits with Jesus to listen and soak up as much teaching as she can&amp;hellip; while Martha busies herself cleaning up the kitchen, putting the leftovers away, and nagging her sister to come and help.  Jesus corrects Martha&amp;rsquo;s priorities, pointing out that Mary has actually chosen better - if Martha would hear directly from Him, sit at His feet, draw close to Him in knowledge - this was to be desired more than a clean countertop, an empty dish sink, a mopped floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, Martha wasn&amp;rsquo;t unhappy that Jesus was teaching in her home, she loved Jesus and she welcomed his teaching and the inevitable guests and mess it generated.  Martha&amp;rsquo;s mistake was to forget, hearing from Jesus herself was of prime importance, that the time had come for her to drop everything, forget her obsession with the home economy, and listen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lesson here for parents interested in how to get their children to sit at Jesus&amp;rsquo; feet, learn His word, meditate on Scripture in that lovely, half-unconscious mental state we&amp;rsquo;re sometimes blessed with.  Like Martha, we want all the right things&amp;hellip; for other people.  We want a rich indwelling of the Word, a music-suffused diet of Scripture, for our children&amp;hellip; and we we want a clean countertop, a mopped floor and a mowed yard, for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;we never enjoy delights like the Psalms - we don&amp;rsquo;t ever get to relish, to drink up, anything contained there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would write checks for huge sums of money, would that suffice to &amp;lsquo;download&amp;rsquo; Scripture directly into their long-term memory - that&amp;rsquo;s how badly we desire good things for them.  For ourselves, though, don&amp;rsquo;t we fall into the trap of distraction, over-attachment to the details, an infatuation with petty things?  And we never enjoy delights like the Psalms - we don&amp;rsquo;t ever get to relish, to drink up, anything contained there.  If only we had a secret longing to get out in front of our children, explore the Psalms and share with them the nuggets of insight we pick up there, how much more success would we have getting them excited about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Psalms are not, &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff.&amp;rdquo;  They are a light unto our path, a joy, a means of inner communion with God&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just for children, this Word.  It&amp;rsquo;s a lie, which says that feeding our children a cultured, rich diet of the Psalms is sacrificial but to spend a lot of that meditative time &amp;amp; energy on ourselves is selfish.  In truth, to avoid infusing ourselves with the Word to where it affects our behavior and demeanor is selfishness itself; children ultimately imitate what they see in our habits, our patterns of enjoyment, not just what we claim adherence to.  If you are a parent, and you are not making deliberate efforts to keep ten steps ahead of your children in this family foray through the Word, then you are falling behind, and your children are leading.  Pushing them out in front of you into the fields of memorization and meditation, will feel to them like isolation.  It will feel academic.  It will feel like &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff&amp;rdquo;.  The Psalms are not, &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff.&amp;rdquo;  They are a light unto our path, a joy, a means of inner communion with God, a battery of spiritual energy and forward potential.  Memorization and a rich, musical intake of Psalms is not just for children, it is for Christians.  Don&amp;rsquo;t leave your children alone to enjoy the best things - be a leader and find those best Psalms, that great music, and enjoy them yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they see you enjoy, by God&amp;rsquo;s grace, they will soon enjoy themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web site !</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:19:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;here-we-go-2017&#34;&gt;Here we go, 2017&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m excited.  It&amp;rsquo;s been a solid 10 years since I&amp;rsquo;ve built a site from scratch, and it&amp;rsquo;s great to see how the tech has changed.  After a lot of knocking about, I&amp;rsquo;ve settled on a great static site engine from the good folks at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.  It&amp;rsquo;s simple enough that I can actually wrap my mind around most of it, and also simple enough that adding content should be pretty painless.  Big shout out for Hugo &amp;ndash; I would recommend it for anyone looking for a fast-rendering, lightweight engine for blogs or simpler websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to getting to know you all, and thanks for stopping by.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring 2017</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;heritage-church-cpc&#34;&gt;Heritage Church CPC&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In February 2017 we will be at Heritage Church in Centerville TN.  Recordings are scheduled for &lt;strong&gt;Psalms #15, 23, 103 and 139.&lt;/strong&gt;  I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to working with all the participating musicians!  Scroll down for details about music selections, including video excerpts of sample performances.  Please comment below to leave us a message!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a preview of what the final production of Psalm #139 might sound like, including narration, please &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/1701c139.mp3&#34;&gt;click here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;for-musicians&#34;&gt;For Musicians&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend of February 20&amp;rsquo;th &lt;em&gt;(still being confirmed&amp;hellip; hang tight)&lt;/em&gt; we&amp;rsquo;ll be recording four pieces of music to accompany the production of four Psalms, which we hope many folks in your community will use as an aid in Scripture memory.  These are fully produced recordings and I expect a high level of focus and ensemble as we work toward giving our best, in service to the church!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will work two coaching sessions into our weekend, with the help of cellist Rebecca Landell-Reed, &lt;em&gt;viola de gambist&lt;/em&gt; and cellist for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apollosfire.org&#34;&gt;Baroque ensemble, &lt;strong&gt;Apollo&amp;rsquo;s Fire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  She will be Skyping into our rehearsals and giving you feedback on musicality and interpretation, before we get down to recording our final tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick video introduction to the music we&amp;rsquo;ll be recording.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/0mKQVw6sKmM&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-15-o-lord-who-shall-dwell-in-thy-house&#34;&gt;Psalm #15 &amp;ldquo;O Lord, Who shall dwell in Thy house&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Psalm #15 (KJV) we have scored the &lt;em&gt;Adagio cantabile&lt;/em&gt; (2nd mov&amp;rsquo;t) of Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s String quartet #2 in G major Opus #18.  Sheet music can &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/97m0ip7gptenq75/Beethoven%20Opus%2018%20Quartet%20no2.zip?dl=0&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;be found here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;em&gt;(right-click to Save As&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensemble roster:&lt;/strong&gt; Violin I, Violin II, Viola, Cello&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to an example performance on YouTube, for reference.  (&lt;em&gt;Please fast-forward to 8 minutes, 30 seconds)&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/Q55TmxeRktM&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-23-the-lord-is-my-shepherd-i-shall-not-want&#34;&gt;Psalm #23 &amp;ldquo;The Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Psalm #23 (KJV) we have scored 2&amp;rsquo;nd movement of Felix Mendellsohn&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Piano Trio no1 in D Major&lt;/em&gt;.  Sheet music can &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/371mv0yudkvvbf0/Mendelssohn%20Trio%20no1%20in%20D%20Minor%20Opus%2049%2C%20All%20parts.zip?dl=0&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;be found here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;em&gt;(right-click to Save As&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensemble roster:&lt;/strong&gt; Piano, Violin, Cello&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to an example performance on YouTube, for reference.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/c5ujAbu_0yc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-103-bless-the-lord-o-my-soul&#34;&gt;Psalm #103 &amp;ldquo;Bless the Lord, O my soul&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Psalm #103 (KJV) we have scored the &lt;em&gt;Andante cantabile&lt;/em&gt; (third) movement from Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s string trio Opus #97 &amp;lsquo;Archduke&amp;rsquo;.  NOTE: Sheet music can &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/40625080/SA/SA/Heritage/Sheet%20music/Beethoven%20Opus%2097%20Piano%20Trio%20in%20Bb%20Major.zip&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;be found here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;em&gt;(right-click to Save As&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to an example performance on YouTube, for reference.  (&lt;em&gt;Please fast-forward to 25 minutes, 19 seconds)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/5mrfy_D9JVE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-139-o-lord-you-have-searched-me&#34;&gt;Psalm #139  &amp;ldquo;O Lord, you have searched me&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Psalm #139 (KJV) we have scored &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_Siloti&#34;&gt;Alexander Siloti&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; keyboard transcription of JS Bach&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Andante&lt;/em&gt; from the &lt;em&gt;Sonata for Violin Solo in A Minor.&lt;/em&gt;  NOTE:  Sheet music can &lt;a href=&#34;https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/siloti.pdf&#34;&gt;be found here:&lt;/a&gt;** &lt;em&gt;(right-click to Save As&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensemble roster:&lt;/strong&gt; Piano solo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to an example performance on YouTube, for reference.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/6tj2y8-_ric&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scripture Audio is dedicated to helping churches, families and individuals absorb the Word of God through the enriching power of classical music.  We believe in the power of music to enable Christians to deeply drink of the meaning of Scripture, to grow in their faith, teach their children, share their gifts, remember the past, and encourage each other.  Our secondary goal is to bring amateur musicians back into service to the believing community by arranging local, on-the-ground recording sessions, joining both the production and consumption of music and Scripture narration in an enjoyable, lasting, and localized process of culture building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rationale&#34;&gt;Rationale&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christians are taught to learn the Word in a music-drenched way (Col. 3:16 &amp;ndash; our theme verse.)  Memorizing individual verses and verse references of the Bible is always appropriate, but if we believe that the Scriptures are both living and active, we&amp;rsquo;re advised to imbibe the Scriptures in a musical way, preferably in large enough &amp;lsquo;chunks&amp;rsquo; that we grasp &lt;em&gt;the context&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-music&#34;&gt;What music?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Scriptures aren&amp;rsquo;t specific as to what appropriate music suited for this task sounds like; but in the spirit of bringing to God the best our culture has to offer, we want to help you and your family choose the best of traditional music as an aid not only in your Bible &lt;em&gt;proficiency&lt;/em&gt;, but in your &lt;em&gt;love for the Word.&lt;/em&gt;  If you ever came across a line in your Bible which had been set to a familiar, perhaps beloved song in your churchgoing past, you know the &amp;lsquo;heart in your mouth&amp;rsquo; feeling as the words suddenly leap off the page and stir the deeper reaches of your heart.  This is the highest and best purpose of music in God&amp;rsquo;s world; men and women were created to resonate best with the truth, when accompanied by the best compositions which resonate with that truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the highest and best purpose of music in God&amp;rsquo;s world; men and women were created to resonate best with the truth, when music which best resonates with that truth accompanies it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-it-works&#34;&gt;How it works&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You listen to audio tracks!  Our organizing principle is, &lt;em&gt;If it isn&amp;rsquo;t easy, we won&amp;rsquo;t do it&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;, and we&amp;rsquo;ve arranged it all around that philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn a portion of Scripture, you&amp;rsquo;ll start out listening to a complete narration of the text, accompanied by some great music.  Over time, slightly altered tracks give you less and less of the Scripture narration, so your mind, clued-in by familiarity with the music, begins to &amp;lsquo;fill in&amp;rsquo; the missing pieces, until you arrive at full mastery of the material.  By this point, the music is typically an unnecessary &amp;lsquo;crutch&amp;rsquo;, since the narration is never rhymed, altered, or set to poetry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These tracks can be listened to in the car, while jogging, on an iPod or cell phone, or over whatever digital device you choose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;family&#34;&gt;Family&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to listen in a family context, if possible!  While you are learning the Scriptures together, you are also growing in a shared, cultural experience of the music &lt;em&gt;in connection&lt;/em&gt; with that passage &amp;ndash; and musical experiences are always best, when they are shared.  The gift of love for music, is a gift meant to be passed on.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based out of Southwest Virginia, our focus is on church communities, home school groups and Christian schools in the Central &amp;amp; Southeast US.  If you would like to inquire regarding a S/A production for your church or school group, or if you&amp;rsquo;d just like to drop us a line, please email us at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scriptureaudio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also check us out on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/ScriptureAudio-1185573308164019/&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ScriptureAudio&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>