<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Your Kids Reach the Limit</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/02/13/17-2-13-when-your-kids-reach-the-limit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/02/13/17-2-13-when-your-kids-reach-the-limit/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t let your pride get in your kids&amp;rsquo; way. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a fresh situation where my kids&amp;rsquo; memorization level in Psalms is starting to approach my own. Pretty soon I&amp;rsquo;ll possess the blessing of a house full of little ones who know as much great material from this book, as I do. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun to be able to &amp;ldquo;check&amp;rdquo; them on mispronounced words, or forgotten phrases, while I&amp;rsquo;m doing chores or working on something else, all from memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is There Meaning in Music?</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/02/06/17-2-6-is-there-meaning-in-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/02/06/17-2-6-is-there-meaning-in-music/</guid>
      <description>Who Exactly Is Working for Who, Here, Anyway. I am often mystified when listen to classical or &amp;ldquo;serious&amp;rdquo; music. The thought bothers me, that this music must over my head, in the sense that it contains a hidden meaning. Like a good public speaker, the music just glows with a kind of baffling organization and purpose, I think it must be telling a kind of wonderful story in a language I don’t speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy?  The Psalms Make Encouragement Easier</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/30/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/30/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</guid>
      <description>When Just Wanting to Say Something Isn&amp;rsquo;t Enough&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m a shy guy, especially if you are having a hard time. It may not seem like it, should we meet, but I find interacting with other people stressful and draining, which is another way of saying I am a natural introvert. Conversations are hard – and conversations with suffering people are harder; when I see a person who has needs, who could obviously use a warm word of encouragement, I feel a little frozen to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/23/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2017/01/23/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</guid>
      <description>Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too In the story of Jesus in the home of Lazarus, Mary &amp;amp; Martha, we see famous scene where Mary sits with Jesus to listen and soak up as much teaching as she can&amp;hellip; while Martha busies herself cleaning up the kitchen, putting the leftovers away, and nagging her sister to come and help. Jesus corrects Martha&amp;rsquo;s priorities, pointing out that Mary has actually chosen better - if Martha would hear directly from Him, sit at His feet, draw close to Him in knowledge - this was to be desired more than a clean countertop, an empty dish sink, a mopped floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web site !</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:19:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</guid>
      <description>Here we go, 2017&amp;hellip; So I&amp;rsquo;m excited. It&amp;rsquo;s been a solid 10 years since I&amp;rsquo;ve built a site from scratch, and it&amp;rsquo;s great to see how the tech has changed. After a lot of knocking about, I&amp;rsquo;ve settled on a great static site engine from the good folks at Hugo. It&amp;rsquo;s simple enough that I can actually wrap my mind around most of it, and also simple enough that adding content should be pretty painless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>Psalm 103, KJV&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;   **Upload date 5/31/17
 Hello Heritage! Ready to memorize a Psalm? This month we are enjoying #103 together in the King James Version, brought to us by Scott Young and your very own Centerville String Quartet. Back in March they recorded the Andante cantabile (third) movement from Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s piano trio Opus #97 &amp;lsquo;Archduke&amp;rsquo;. What a pairing with Psalm 103! We hope your family will enjoy it as much as mine will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Purpose Scripture Audio is dedicated to helping churches, families and individuals absorb the Word of God through the enriching power of classical music. We believe in the power of music to enable Christians to deeply drink of the meaning of Scripture, to grow in their faith, teach their children, share their gifts, remember the past, and encourage each other. Our secondary goal is to bring amateur musicians back into service to the believing community by arranging local, on-the-ground recording sessions, joining both the production and consumption of music and Scripture narration in an enjoyable, lasting, and localized process of culture building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Based out of Southwest Virginia, our focus is on church communities, home school groups and Christian schools in the Central &amp;amp; Southeast US. If you would like to inquire regarding a S/A production for your church or school group, or if you&amp;rsquo;d just like to drop us a line, please email us at ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.
Also check us out on Facebook and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>