<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-139-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 139, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/344999336&amp;amp;color=%23ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Version 1, Upload date 10/2/17
**Download an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/uj0462oq8phhsk1/SA1701d_V1.mp3?dl=0&#34;&gt;MP3 of Psalm 139, Version 1 here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good morning Heritage, and welcome to October!  We&amp;rsquo;ve been memorizing a Psalm bimonthly since June, and this will be our last month together before the holiday season begins in earnest.  As a bonus for sticking with us through Psalm 15, Psalm 103 and now Psalm 139, we&amp;rsquo;ll be emailing you a separation memorization set for Psalm 23 to use with your young &amp;lsquo;uns, at the end of the month!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month&amp;rsquo;s setting of Psalm 139 is JS Bach&amp;rsquo;s  Andante from the Sonata for Violin Solo in A minor, transcribed for the piano by the Alexander Siloti and performed by Christy Stouffer.  Thanks to Christy for her interpretation of this pensive piece, recorded at the end of a very long and exhausting day for her directing choral and ensemble numbers!  Thanks once again to Scott Young for providing the voiceover.
Here is the link to the page you&amp;rsquo;ll visit every day this month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re using a phone or tablet, you may want to copy-paste the address of this page directly onto your home screen.  It will create an icon, like an app, which will take you directly to the site with no fussing around every day to find your way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instructions:  Simple - gather the family and listen about 3 times in a row every day.  That&amp;rsquo;s it.  Try to find a time where things are fairly calm, when everyone is settled down and able to listen with relative attention.  The goal is not to be able to recite the Psalm this week - it&amp;rsquo;s to absorb the text through familiarity with the music, like soaking in a nice, hot bathtub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, do it again.  Easy, right?  You&amp;rsquo;ll hear from me again in about a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any experiences or tips to share about using this track?  Please share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Your Kids Reach the Limit</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-2-13-when-your-kids-reach-the-limit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-2-13-when-your-kids-reach-the-limit/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;don-t-let-your-pride-get-in-your-kids-way&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t let your pride get in your kids&amp;rsquo; way.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a fresh situation where my kids&amp;rsquo; memorization level in Psalms is starting to approach my own.  Pretty soon I&amp;rsquo;ll possess the blessing of a house full of little ones who know as much great material from this book, as I do.  It&amp;rsquo;s been fun to be able to &amp;ldquo;check&amp;rdquo; them on mispronounced words, or forgotten phrases, while I&amp;rsquo;m doing chores or working on something else, all from memory.  It&amp;rsquo;s rather effortless because the material is already &lt;em&gt;in there&lt;/em&gt;, in mental RAM so to speak. The task of getting up and doing Scripture memory with them every day seemed no great challenge in the past, and my motivation level was always high.  Of course we all have certain chores that are onerous, like mopping the floors in my case (hate mopping&amp;hellip;).  Scripture memory so far as not been that chore.  It&amp;rsquo;s been more along the lines of excitement, like &amp;ldquo;Hey kids, there is the great Psalm I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to share with you!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now the party is  over.  As they essentially surpass my knowledge level, I feel a hesitation which I can&amp;rsquo;t quite place my finger on.  A feeling of &lt;em&gt;resistance&lt;/em&gt;, as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Do-Work-Overcome-Resistance-Your/dp/1936891379&#34;&gt;Steven Pressfield&lt;/a&gt; might say.  The motivation has slipped away.  I guess the children are wading into waters I haven&amp;rsquo;t explored myself, and that brings with it a sense of trepidation, like I suppose anyone might feel about something new.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been procrastinating on prepping new Psalms for them to start in on, and the reason has nothing to do with their readiness for the material - I have every reason to believe they&amp;rsquo;ll be as curious about them as they were, about the others.  The reason is all about me and my very human reticence about pushing through what I &lt;em&gt;perceive&lt;/em&gt; as a threshold or &amp;ldquo;glass ceiling&amp;rdquo;, the boundary of my own knowledge where I feel comfortable, and moving into an area where I don&amp;rsquo;t feel as comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s obviously a misplaced and faithless kind of anxiety that would set a poor limit on how much of the Scriptures my children learn, &lt;em&gt;namely my own limit.&lt;/em&gt;  There is - may I say this with a kindly Internet smile - a sort of pride in knowing more than your children.  Right?  There can be fear of your children perceiving that you really don&amp;rsquo;t know as much as they thought you did.  What will they &lt;em&gt;think&lt;/em&gt; of you then?  Will you lose just a teensy bit of respectability in their eyes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is &amp;hellip; a sort of pride in knowing more than your children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you deal with this situation?  Sometimes just naming our problems is half the battle, and if you also struggle with these kind of natural barriers to forward movement into new and unexplored areas in parenting, let me encourage you to name that fear, that laziness if you like.   I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been getting wisdom from &lt;a href=&#34;https://michaelhyatt.com/two-postures-toward-change.html&#34;&gt;Michael Hyatt&lt;/a&gt; where he encourages &lt;em&gt;leaning in&lt;/em&gt; to these growth areas, even if it feels uncomfortable.  Get personal with the issue; move up to it, look it square in the face, then prayerfully suss out the answers to, &amp;ldquo;why am I averse to forward movement, with confidence, in this area?&amp;rdquo;  Then take the first small step toward tackling it.  We all love the line from CS Lewis where the Narnia characters charge deeper into the heavenly kingdom saying, &amp;ldquo;Higher up and further in!&amp;rdquo;  We know we aren&amp;rsquo;t given over to a spirit of &lt;em&gt;fear&lt;/em&gt;.  So what is keeping you from letting your children go where you haven&amp;rsquo;t gone before?  Are there any tips you can share from your own experience?  Share with the rest of us down below.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is There Meaning in Music?</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-2-6-is-there-meaning-in-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-2-6-is-there-meaning-in-music/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;who-exactly-is-working-for-who-here-anyway&#34;&gt;Who Exactly Is Working for Who, Here, Anyway.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am often mystified when listen to classical or &amp;ldquo;serious&amp;rdquo; music. The thought bothers me, that this music must over my head, in the sense that it contains a hidden meaning.  Like a good public speaker, the music just &lt;em&gt;glows&lt;/em&gt; with a kind of baffling organization and purpose, I think it must be telling a kind of wonderful story in a language I don’t speak. Have you ever kept your reaction to music in suspense? I&amp;rsquo;ll wonder what the composer meant by their composition, and when I&amp;rsquo;m unable figure it out just by listening, I&amp;rsquo;m uncomfortable deciding how I feel about it. I want to track down an expert who can help me: another musician maybe, or printed liner notes from the CD jacket. Without more insight I think it will stay over my head, which means enjoying it is kind of out of reach; I give up – this music may be part of my cultural heritage, but it goes back in the drawer, and I believe myself cut off from understanding the message it must surely have for me. Sigh. Oh, well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s benefit in learning about composers, of course - the history surrounding them, their personal stories, and in doing academic analysis of their writing. But on a personal level, in trying to &lt;em&gt;rescue&lt;/em&gt; my feeling of connection with great music, I’ve found it helpful to make a separation between &lt;em&gt;seriousness&lt;/em&gt; in music, and its &lt;em&gt;meaning&lt;/em&gt;. The two are not the same. Our Christian enthusiasm for the persistence of literal meaning in the written word, in Scripture, and in serious dialogue about the important things, is well-founded and remains critical in defending our faith from attack; but I don’t think the enthusiasm should not extend, in a sort of metaphorical way, into the area of music. The musical disciplines are too weak for that. We can&amp;rsquo;t hold them to the standard we hold words to - the material simply falls apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe height=&#34;350&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; style=&#34;display: block !important; height: 350px !important; &#34; scrolling=&#34;0&#34; frameBorder=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;//renderer.qmerce.com/interaction/58ac424d7e8066d7630d5638&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a thought experiment, how would one prove the truth or falsity of a proposition communicated through music? Can there be musical debate? Can there be ‘conversation’ between instruments that the rest of us could reliably interpret? Strictly speaking, no. Music can be said to speak, but not as with words. Music involves conversation, but not like two actual people talking. Music involves communication of meaning, &lt;em&gt;but not the literal kind&lt;/em&gt;; music contains something &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; thought and question within it, but not in any literary sense involving &lt;em&gt;accountability&lt;/em&gt;. For example if you speak a sentence in English to me, and I fail to grasp your meaning, there may be a moral dimension to my lapse; perhaps I am a bad listener, or I allowed myself to become distracted. In short, I am probably rude, because unless you use tedious or bizarre vocabulary you may &lt;em&gt;reasonably expect me&lt;/em&gt; to understand you. However if you play me a song on a xylophone and I fail to catch your meaning, I should not feel too badly about it.  Everyone understands, xylophones can be a little vague in their vocabulary, and if our musical chat falls apart, the presumption of guilt remains on the xylophone, not me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the strength of music does not concentrate in the communication of &lt;em&gt;meaning&lt;/em&gt;, in the strict sense. I think its great and subtle power lies in a sort of additive, magnifying, multiplicative, companionlike, superpowerish, mysterious and slightly fishy ability to come alongside and give a boost to something &lt;em&gt;else&lt;/em&gt; - a text perhaps - anything greater and more specific than itself, either in literal content, or in purpose. That purpose or event needs to already be plainly understood by all participants, for music to do its business. A dance, a worship service, a funeral, a rave, a nightclub. In all of these places, at each of these events, &lt;em&gt;everyone is there for the same reason.&lt;/em&gt; No explanation is needed for the music; for how it adds value, for why it sounds that peculiar way, for why it is so unbearably loud; the meaning of the music is obvious, because the meaning &lt;em&gt;of the event is obvious&lt;/em&gt;. Music is the &lt;em&gt;meta&lt;/em&gt; to the larger &lt;em&gt;message&lt;/em&gt;, the &amp;lsquo;how&amp;rsquo; to the larger &amp;lsquo;what&amp;rsquo;. The event is the main attraction, the &lt;em&gt;raison d&amp;rsquo;etre&lt;/em&gt; - music is the &lt;em&gt;oo-la-la.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this way music functions for us as a kind of cultural co-pilot, contributing a &lt;em&gt;superabundance&lt;/em&gt; of meaning to any human effort which can already stand on its own ten toes. Even in their simplicity, for example, country songs can be recited dryly like a poem, and everyone understands the &lt;em&gt;meaning&lt;/em&gt;: the lonely cowboy loses his truck, goes fishing, shoots his dog, meets a girl. But who would remember that poem, without the salty-sweet tune? The tune injects a secret sauce, a marinade of meaning, into that over-done steak of a poem, and suddenly - &lt;em&gt;Bam&lt;/em&gt; - it’s delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Likewise I suppose a group of dancers could dance silently without music. Participants in a rave or rock concert could do whatever they do without the music. A funeral could take place in silence; but we needn&amp;rsquo;t work too hard to grasp that all these are better with music. The music spreads icing on the cake; it fills in and rounds out the stodginess and pragmatism of life; it relishes meat onto the bones of &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; human experiences. It functions best not as the object of consideration, but when &lt;em&gt;subjected&lt;/em&gt; to a secondary role - the role of accompaniment. When assigned to the task at hand, when set to work as it were, music comes fully into its own mysterious powers to provoke all the emotional capacities of the people, and collimate them into a single, focused beam. Here we see music &lt;em&gt;working&lt;/em&gt;, working alongside us toward a higher purpose; it is subjected, purposed and repurposed, in a most delightful way, and we’re all happy about it. The music doesn’t mind. As long as we don’t &lt;em&gt;abuse&lt;/em&gt; it, subjection in this way is not the downfall of music, &lt;em&gt;it is its glory.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is perhaps most useful to redefine our understanding of music as subjective, in exactly that sense. It is our willing &lt;em&gt;subject&lt;/em&gt;, bringing home the aesthetic bacon, frosting additional layers of &lt;em&gt;delight&lt;/em&gt; to the meaning we &lt;em&gt;assign&lt;/em&gt; to life and its pursuits. The meaning of the music itself, as it were, is redefined as its contemporary effect upon us. Yes, I said it: contemporary. In the moment. Fresh. Contextualized. Immediate.  Under our control. We assign it the context; it goes to work &lt;em&gt;for us.&lt;/em&gt; Its meaning is derivative, helpful in a complementary sense, yes, with all the loadiness of that loaded term. If we find a certain bit of music brightens up our wedding ceremony, our funeral meditation, or our folk dance, we are as free to decorate our event with this or that musical number, as we are to decorate our living room wall with concert posters, medieval tapestries, finger-paintings, tree trimmings, cereal box tops, or that thing from Target. Our taste may be questioned - our right to purpose and re-purpose our possessions &lt;em&gt;may not&lt;/em&gt;. Music in this way is a kind of shared, communal possession, which is still in every sense ours individually. It is the original open-source software: infinitely reproducible, downloadable for tinkering, adaptable, freely available to any and all takers - precious like water, but free like the wind. It is meant to be used, not hoarded or held over the heads of others as a status symbol - its value comes from its adaptability, its utility from its commodity, its suitability from its mutability. So then, subjectivity in this sense is the great weakness of music, as well as its endearing glory; it is weak, not like rottenness is the weakness of wood, but like woman is the weakness of man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The more we can grasp that music works for us, the more free we&amp;rsquo;ll feel from anxiety whether we “get” the &lt;em&gt;serious&lt;/em&gt; stuff. Serious music is its own genre, its own category among others; it is no better and no worse than less-serious music. It is what it is, and to the degree that life itself can be serious, we probably need serious music. But as our attention migrates from unserious to serious material, the true source of meaning does not magically and simultaneously migrate from ourselves, and from the seriousness of our own life experiences, into the music itself. This is not a battle of standing between ourselves and the composer, as if by virtue of writing a symphony instead of a country song the fellow’s compositions suddenly deserve to be treated more seriously than we treat our actual lives. Our purposes as humans come first. We may miss the subtleties of his workmanship, but we are at liberty not to find his products useful. He may be the best vendor of his musical wares, but we are free not to buy, and not to listen. The choice is ours, because our life is more ours, than his. We may empoverish ourselves through such choices, and I would encourage you not to - but the choice must always and emphatically remain ours. The music works for us. We supply the meaning; he supplies the soundtrack. We throw the party; he brings the Chinette and the napkins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in developing a habit of appreciation for serious music, our first step is to reclaim the notion that life itself is quite serious business; that some subjects are worthy of more sober consideration, and that for this music to find a home within us, we must make a home &lt;em&gt;for it.&lt;/em&gt; Great music is like a great painting or a piece of fine furniture: before hauling it back from Sotheby&amp;rsquo;s, the question must at some point be asked, &amp;ldquo;Where are we going to &lt;em&gt;put&lt;/em&gt; this thing?&amp;rdquo; One may find that a large and valuable collection of Rococo mahogany furniture may fit into a double-wide trailer only with some awkwardness. So ponder out a plausible &lt;em&gt;context&lt;/em&gt; for the CD that challenges you, and pause to ask the question, &amp;ldquo;Is this really the music for me?&amp;rdquo; A perfectly good answer is, &amp;ldquo;Mmkay, no&amp;rdquo;. There is no shame in putting the works of a great composer back on the shelf, if the subtle or not-so-subtle characteristics of the piece, simply don&amp;rsquo;t fit in your spiritual house. Remember, it &lt;em&gt;works&lt;/em&gt; for you. Explore and reject with gleeful abandon, as befitteth saints; exercise your right as a consumer of music; listen once to that CD you borrowed, then give it back. You have your own musical interests and standards of usefulness. Some people like to hang their garden tools on pegboards, and some like to put them on shelves – music should sit squarely in this mental category of “Meh.” Act accordingly. March gaily through the whole iTunes store with dirty boots on; feel free to look and not buy a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For myself, this means a perspective adjustment, and an increase of courage. Americans are constantly complaining about other Americans&amp;rsquo; commercialized and mercenary taste in music. We loudly complain that our nation has no taste, no respect for history, no reverence for high art; yet if this were true, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t we be listening irreverently to vast quantities of freely available classical music on YouTube, recklessly consuming string quartets on our iPods and mindlessly debating the merits of this or that conductor without regard for how much we really knew about conducting? Or are we only that way about politics? No &amp;ndash; we are offered a free concert, and instead of going in a tee shirt and chewing gum during the quiet parts, we look away with shame, mumble, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;No thanks&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; and slink away like scalded dogs. We wouldn’t go see great art if someone begged us to take the tickets. This is not the behavior of mischievous and enthusiastic capitalism; this is &lt;em&gt;fear.&lt;/em&gt; We are afraid of serious music, because we think it has greater meaning than we have a place for in our hearts. We are afraid that we&amp;rsquo;ll be outclassed and out-thought by music somehow smarter than we are. We Americans don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;re too good for such music - we think it is too good &lt;em&gt;for us.&lt;/em&gt; It would never occur to put such music to work for us - no, we supposedly feckless consumers imagine up a requirement to listen &lt;em&gt;properly&lt;/em&gt; with a furrowed brow, wearing a tweed smoking jacket and a satin cummerbund, pondering lyrics translated from the original German, in order for us to be worthy &lt;em&gt;of it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all bosh, of course. If you ever open your Bible and read what&amp;rsquo;s there, a moment necessarily exists in your life where your mind encounters truly serious things. There is great meaning on that page - truths with lasting significance. Own it. A true Christian is a sober-minded Christian - he is a &lt;em&gt;serious&lt;/em&gt; person, at a transformational level. Given access to great music, a Christian may find great utility and usefulness there, if a connection can be made between the depth and import implied in the music, and the actual purposes of God. No rule-book exists how this connection might be made; humanity has &lt;em&gt;improvised&lt;/em&gt; this thing called &amp;ldquo;joyful noise&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;musical meditation&amp;rdquo; for many thousands of years. There are few hard and fast rules. But there are horses for courses, and for the hard course of the Christian life, only a certain kind of horse will do for &lt;em&gt;you.&lt;/em&gt; There’s your subjectivity birthday cake; you can &lt;em&gt;eat&lt;/em&gt; it, too. How can serious music serve &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; purposes, as a Christian? How can it bring additional meaning, to the meaning we see plainly in Scripture?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figure that out, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be on your way to fulfilling the directive: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Let the word of Christ dwell in you richly in all wisdom; teaching and admonishing one another in psalms and hymns and spiritual songs, singing with grace in your hearts to the Lord&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shy?  The Psalms Make Encouragement Easier</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/17-1-30-shy-psalms-make-encouragement-easier/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;when-just-wanting-to-say-something-isn-t-enough&#34;&gt;When Just Wanting to Say Something Isn&amp;rsquo;t Enough&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a shy guy, especially if &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; are having a hard time. It may not seem like it, should we meet, but I find interacting with other people stressful and draining, which is another way of saying I am a natural introvert. Conversations are hard – and conversations with suffering people are harder; when I see a person who has needs, who could obviously use a warm word of encouragement, I feel a little frozen to the ground. Unsure what to say, the right words don’t simply materialize in my brain. The more often this happens, the more discouraged I become, wondering, could I ever strengthen others?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever felt this way? Does your heart go out to that friend, mired in a dark season of life or battling trials – only to find when you see them, you have nothing to say? or that when you do speak, what falls out of your mouth falls far short of the good you intended?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picture for a moment the challenge of encouragement could be reduced from art to organization; would that help? Think of an artist painting a beautiful image from a brilliant, imaginative concept in his mind – then picture yourself outdoors on your covered porch, arranging the tables and chairs in proper order; which seems easier? As an introvert I tend think of encouragement as a difficult and mystical art form; but what if it were less like a burst of artistic imagination, and more a (relatively) mundane task of putting some words, like furniture, into the right place? Would we be more likely to actually practice it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine for a moment the challenge of encouragement could be reduced from art to organization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Psalms are full of material ready-made for the purpose of encouragement. They are a natural fit just by their construction, their focus. They tend to lean less on doctrine or on instruction for life, and more on exploring the inner workings of the heart. The language there is illustrative; it sends light into the deep crevices in the human experience with honesty and energy and a tender, faithful grace which we couldn’t hope to duplicate, were we to sit down with pen and paper and spend years trying. The Psalms are, after all, the word of God, despite their source straight from the experiences of a man; they are paradoxical in that sense - an undistorted, mirror-like reflection of our real life, read back to us in reverse as it were, through the glass of God’s truth and grace. In the mystery at work, there is no dilution or minimization of God’s power on the one hand, or of the pain and joy of the human condition, on the other. The Psalms are a compact miracle of clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are also the inheritance of every Christian, and we should lay claim on this enormous mineral deposit of material. For believers who want to encourage others, it’s our time to find a pickaxe and shovel, to find a suitable point of ground and start digging. The Psalms are meant for sharing, in good times but particularly in bad; with the glad, but also with souls stuck in the deep and airless recesses of life. There are resources in this book here which bring life and the sunshine of hope to those who have no hope; words which provoke a lifeless faith; phrases that can be broken down like nuggets, packed with rich gold. Hope and faith are here in the context of anxiety, deep depression, panic, adversity, fear, temptation and any trouble. There is no lack in the love of God found here toward you, to match the trouble you might find in your own experience; these words are conceived in the mind of God with care and deep consideration, the same care that formed your physical body “…intricately woven in the depths of the earth, Your eyes saw my unformed substance…” (Ps. 139) These words are personal, they are meant for you, and for this life full of trouble and care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must not give fools’ gold when we could have shared the real thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And they are not meant to be topped, when you share them with others. They are not meant to be replicated or imitated – we must feel no great need to speak ad-lib like a kind of spiritual stand-up comic, “in the spirit of the Bible”, making “the truth our own” as goes the expression. There is a time to just sit and listen, but when the moment comes to speak, we must not give fools’ gold when we could have shared the real thing. Is it real love, to share with our neighbor less than the best? Encouragement means sharing the Word with our hurting brother; we should not redefine it as a misguided effort at creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, rearrange and index Scriptures in your mind; put your creativity to work at the job of placing a finger on just the right bit of a Psalm for your particular friend, the one with that particular &lt;em&gt;thing&lt;/em&gt;. With enough of the Word at your mental fingertips, this job becomes more routine; it becomes attainable – it becomes enjoyable. This is a task of mastery and memorization, not of inspiration; the bit of Scripture you want isn’t really out of reach – duplicating it and its power, is. We were not meant for such a task – God has prepared good works for us to do, and if encouragement is a good work, we must believe that his Word prepares us for that effort. If we will read the Psalms and take them to heart, we will see that it amply supplies us for encouraging others. When we quote them, we will have confidence, as there will never be a question that we are falling short of the truth. That confidence will give rise to a greater interest in serving others, and make us more enthusiastic in pursuit of more material to store up for the task.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If encouragement is a good work, we must believe that his Word prepares us for that effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get the Psalms into your heart, so you can encourage yourself; but double your efforts, if you want to use them to encourage others. Don’t be shy about it. You may find that inhibition will no longer be the obstacle to encouragement it once was; you’ll instead see reason for thankfulness, that you have been given a “word in season”, just in that moment when you most desire to speak it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/16-1-23-psalms-are-for-adults-too/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;parents-the-psalms-are-for-adults-too&#34;&gt;Parents: The Psalms are for adults, too&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the story of Jesus in the home of Lazarus, Mary &amp;amp; Martha, we see famous scene where Mary sits with Jesus to listen and soak up as much teaching as she can&amp;hellip; while Martha busies herself cleaning up the kitchen, putting the leftovers away, and nagging her sister to come and help.  Jesus corrects Martha&amp;rsquo;s priorities, pointing out that Mary has actually chosen better - if Martha would hear directly from Him, sit at His feet, draw close to Him in knowledge - this was to be desired more than a clean countertop, an empty dish sink, a mopped floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, Martha wasn&amp;rsquo;t unhappy that Jesus was teaching in her home, she loved Jesus and she welcomed his teaching and the inevitable guests and mess it generated.  Martha&amp;rsquo;s mistake was to forget, hearing from Jesus herself was of prime importance, that the time had come for her to drop everything, forget her obsession with the home economy, and listen!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lesson here for parents interested in how to get their children to sit at Jesus&amp;rsquo; feet, learn His word, meditate on Scripture in that lovely, half-unconscious mental state we&amp;rsquo;re sometimes blessed with.  Like Martha, we want all the right things&amp;hellip; for other people.  We want a rich indwelling of the Word, a music-suffused diet of Scripture, for our children&amp;hellip; and we we want a clean countertop, a mopped floor and a mowed yard, for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;we never enjoy delights like the Psalms - we don&amp;rsquo;t ever get to relish, to drink up, anything contained there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would write checks for huge sums of money, would that suffice to &amp;lsquo;download&amp;rsquo; Scripture directly into their long-term memory - that&amp;rsquo;s how badly we desire good things for them.  For ourselves, though, don&amp;rsquo;t we fall into the trap of distraction, over-attachment to the details, an infatuation with petty things?  And we never enjoy delights like the Psalms - we don&amp;rsquo;t ever get to relish, to drink up, anything contained there.  If only we had a secret longing to get out in front of our children, explore the Psalms and share with them the nuggets of insight we pick up there, how much more success would we have getting them excited about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Psalms are not, &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff.&amp;rdquo;  They are a light unto our path, a joy, a means of inner communion with God&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just for children, this Word.  It&amp;rsquo;s a lie, which says that feeding our children a cultured, rich diet of the Psalms is sacrificial but to spend a lot of that meditative time &amp;amp; energy on ourselves is selfish.  In truth, to avoid infusing ourselves with the Word to where it affects our behavior and demeanor is selfishness itself; children ultimately imitate what they see in our habits, our patterns of enjoyment, not just what we claim adherence to.  If you are a parent, and you are not making deliberate efforts to keep ten steps ahead of your children in this family foray through the Word, then you are falling behind, and your children are leading.  Pushing them out in front of you into the fields of memorization and meditation, will feel to them like isolation.  It will feel academic.  It will feel like &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff&amp;rdquo;.  The Psalms are not, &amp;ldquo;kid&amp;rsquo;s stuff.&amp;rdquo;  They are a light unto our path, a joy, a means of inner communion with God, a battery of spiritual energy and forward potential.  Memorization and a rich, musical intake of Psalms is not just for children, it is for Christians.  Don&amp;rsquo;t leave your children alone to enjoy the best things - be a leader and find those best Psalms, that great music, and enjoy them yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they see you enjoy, by God&amp;rsquo;s grace, they will soon enjoy themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web site !</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/16-12-31-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:19:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/articles/16-12-31-new-website/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;here-we-go-2017&#34;&gt;Here we go, 2017&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m excited.  It&amp;rsquo;s been a solid 10 years since I&amp;rsquo;ve built a site from scratch, and it&amp;rsquo;s great to see how the tech has changed.  After a lot of knocking about, I&amp;rsquo;ve settled on a great static site engine from the good folks at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.  It&amp;rsquo;s simple enough that I can actually wrap my mind around most of it, and also simple enough that adding content should be pretty painless.  Big shout out for Hugo &amp;ndash; I would recommend it for anyone looking for a fast-rendering, lightweight engine for blogs or simpler websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to getting to know you all, and thanks for stopping by.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>// FAQ //</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/faq/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-this&#34;&gt;What is this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Jonathon Landell, Jr.  I record musical soundtracks for spoken-word narrations of the Bible, primarily Psalms.  You can memorize the Scriptures effortlessly just by listening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christians generally want to learn God&amp;rsquo;s word - by heart.  But this involves more drudgery than most of us have overcome so far through willpower alone.  Staring silently at a page of Scripture at 6am, with nothing to help except a cold cup of coffee is&amp;hellip; tough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great soundtrack makes memorizing Scripture not awful, and not time-intensive.  Music lubricates your mental process, so you&amp;rsquo;ll get more memorized in the course of a year, with much less time spent every day.  How great is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even better, truly great music from the great composers transcends our diet of commercial drivel - and avoids insulting the passage&amp;rsquo;s delicacy and seriousness.  We carefully select classical music that fits a passage - really good stuff, recorded professionally and performed by musicians you would be happy to support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joy and peace are deepened by a good musical setting; like a fine wine or a verse from Handel&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Messiah&amp;rsquo; which leaps from the page when we stumble across it, passages come to vivid life when paired tastefully to a musical arrangement.  Music settles the text into nooks and crannies in the subconscious and lodges it seamlessly into long-term memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn&amp;rsquo;t that what we&amp;rsquo;re after?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-the-text-rhymed-or-sung-or-something&#34;&gt;Is the text rhymed or sung, or something?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.  It&amp;rsquo;s read quite straight, with a natural cadence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-translations-do-you-use&#34;&gt;What translations do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The King James version (KJV) only, thanks to the glories of copyright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-only-classical-music&#34;&gt;Why only classical music?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Returning to the wine analogy, &amp;ldquo;classical&amp;rdquo; is shorthand for music which has aged gracefully.  It&amp;rsquo;s the ribeye steak you could never tire of, the dress that never goes out of style, the Shelby Cobra which will always be a &amp;ldquo;classic car&amp;rdquo;.  Great music is crafted with skill, passion and transcendental understanding; it stands the test of time.  Why not use the best?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, it&amp;rsquo;s royalty-free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-much-does-memorization-material-cost&#34;&gt;How much does memorization material cost?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see it available for download - help yourself.  But see below&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-you-sell-records&#34;&gt;Do you sell records?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not exactly.  Congregations get most excited about musicians they know, so if we can arrange a recording session with their talent pool, using arrangements tailored to their talents, we get the best results.  Recordings are healthy for culture building; they encourage the musicians and inspire a proper and natural pride and sense of satisfaction.  High production values are good, but the personal connection is too valuable to sacrifice for unrealistic, high standards. A recording of even moderate quality can be a source of long lasting enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-narrates-the-biblical-text&#34;&gt;Who narrates the Biblical text?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s best for a member of the local congregation to volunteer as a narrator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-m-a-musician-pastor-can-you-work-with-me-my-church-musicians&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a musician/pastor.  Can you work with me/my church musicians?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send in an email with details! &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scripture.audio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;scripture.audio@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-do-you-do-this&#34;&gt;Why do you do this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s fun!  This started as a way to teach my own kids the Psalms in a radically efficient, engaging way.  It was enjoyable and so effective I started looking for an opportunity to share tracks with others.  Recording, performance and composition are skills I can apply to helping the church; I hope to give opportunity to more semi-professional or amateur musicians who want to serve the body of Christ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-m-curious-about-your-studio-what-do-you-use-to-make-recordings&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m curious about your studio.  What do you use to make recordings?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ears make records, not equipment.  But I enjoy using KRK monitors.  Microphones are from Neumann, DPA, Beyerdynamic and custom active ribbon microphones from Mark Fouxman of Samar Audio in Salt Lake City (VL37a serial #77 and #78).  Preamplification and A/D/A bit wrangling is by Audient (UK) and AppSys Pro Audio (Switzerland).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To drop a line, please email at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scriptureaudio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am active on Instagram at ScriptureAudio2017.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To drop a line, please email at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scriptureaudio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am active on Instagram at ScriptureAudio2017.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>