<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 21:57:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Routines</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-routine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 21:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-routine/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;good-routines-easy-routines&#34;&gt;Good routines = Easy routines&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve seen the value of a highly consistent routine in several areas, in the last few years: bedtime, mealtime, school subjects, bookkeeping for the business, fitness, etc.  It seems that everybody knows that the trick to success in any pursuit, isn&amp;rsquo;t a trick - it&amp;rsquo;s consistent adherence to a good schedule.  This isn&amp;rsquo;t any less true in the important work of cultivating the living Word in yourself, or in your children.  Daily review of material, even if it isn&amp;rsquo;t as varied or fast-moving as you would prefer, is the ticket to year-over-year success, as more and more material is tucked away in the heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What isn&amp;rsquo;t appreciated, is that the &lt;em&gt;more accessible&lt;/em&gt; a routine is, the &lt;em&gt;easier&lt;/em&gt; it is to stick to it.  I tend to set goals way high.  If I try to get settled in an incredibly demanding fitness routine, failure inevitably results; I get overawed, frustrated, disappointed at a goal I can&amp;rsquo;t reasonably reach.  But if I make a routine out of small exercises scattered throughout the day - for example, while slowly listening through the phone tree of a company switchboard, watching a pot getting ready to boil, or waiting for the girls to put their shoes and coats on - before the day is out I&amp;rsquo;ve done the lion&amp;rsquo;s share of a workout, with no time lost, and no sweaty clothes.  But how about those sore muscles!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology is a gift - let&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; it, not &lt;em&gt;abuse&lt;/em&gt; it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal at Scripture Audio is to make your routine of regular Scripture intake as simple as going online and clicking &amp;lsquo;Play&amp;rsquo;.  Technology is a gift - let&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; it, not &lt;em&gt;abuse&lt;/em&gt; it.  Our intent is remove as many stumbling blocks from your path as possible, and maximize the impact the routine has on you.  We keep it simple.  Because routines may be the key to success, but &lt;em&gt;ease of use&lt;/em&gt; is what makes sure that key, stays on your key ring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you use our material or find another path, find a way to smooth down that path as much as possible.  Remember that your goal is not to be a hero - it&amp;rsquo;s to be consistent.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web site !</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:19:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2016/12/31/16-12-31-new-website/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;here-we-go-2017&#34;&gt;Here we go, 2017&amp;hellip;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m excited.  It&amp;rsquo;s been a solid 10 years since I&amp;rsquo;ve built a site from scratch, and it&amp;rsquo;s great to see how the tech has changed.  After a lot of knocking about, I&amp;rsquo;ve settled on a great static site engine from the good folks at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.  It&amp;rsquo;s simple enough that I can actually wrap my mind around most of it, and also simple enough that adding content should be pretty painless.  Big shout out for Hugo &amp;ndash; I would recommend it for anyone looking for a fast-rendering, lightweight engine for blogs or simpler websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to getting to know you all, and thanks for stopping by.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>