<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>// FAQ //</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/faq/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-this&#34;&gt;What is this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Jonathon Landell, Jr.  I record musical soundtracks for spoken-word narrations of the Bible, primarily Psalms.  You can memorize the Scriptures effortlessly just by listening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christians generally want to learn God&amp;rsquo;s word - by heart.  But this involves more drudgery than most of us have overcome so far through willpower alone.  Staring silently at a page of Scripture at 6am, with nothing to help except a cold cup of coffee is&amp;hellip; tough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great soundtrack makes memorizing Scripture not awful, and not time-intensive.  Music lubricates your mental process, so you&amp;rsquo;ll get more memorized in the course of a year, with much less time spent every day.  How great is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even better, truly great music from the great composers transcends our diet of commercial drivel - and avoids insulting the passage&amp;rsquo;s delicacy and seriousness.  We carefully select classical music that fits a passage - really good stuff, recorded professionally and performed by musicians you would be happy to support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joy and peace are deepened by a good musical setting; like a fine wine or a verse from Handel&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Messiah&amp;rsquo; which leaps from the page when we stumble across it, passages come to vivid life when paired tastefully to a musical arrangement.  Music settles the text into nooks and crannies in the subconscious and lodges it seamlessly into long-term memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isn&amp;rsquo;t that what we&amp;rsquo;re after?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-the-text-rhymed-or-sung-or-something&#34;&gt;Is the text rhymed or sung, or something?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No.  It&amp;rsquo;s read quite straight, with a natural cadence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-translations-do-you-use&#34;&gt;What translations do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The King James version (KJV) only, thanks to the glories of copyright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-only-classical-music&#34;&gt;Why only classical music?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Returning to the wine analogy, &amp;ldquo;classical&amp;rdquo; is shorthand for music which has aged gracefully.  It&amp;rsquo;s the ribeye steak you could never tire of, the dress that never goes out of style, the Shelby Cobra which will always be a &amp;ldquo;classic car&amp;rdquo;.  Great music is crafted with skill, passion and transcendental understanding; it stands the test of time.  Why not use the best?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides, it&amp;rsquo;s royalty-free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-much-does-memorization-material-cost&#34;&gt;How much does memorization material cost?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see it available for download - help yourself.  But see below&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-you-sell-records&#34;&gt;Do you sell records?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not exactly.  Congregations get most excited about musicians they know, so if we can arrange a recording session with their talent pool, using arrangements tailored to their talents, we get the best results.  Recordings are healthy for culture building; they encourage the musicians and inspire a proper and natural pride and sense of satisfaction.  High production values are good, but the personal connection is too valuable to sacrifice for unrealistic, high standards. A recording of even moderate quality can be a source of long lasting enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-narrates-the-biblical-text&#34;&gt;Who narrates the Biblical text?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s best for a member of the local congregation to volunteer as a narrator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-m-a-musician-pastor-can-you-work-with-me-my-church-musicians&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a musician/pastor.  Can you work with me/my church musicians?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send in an email with details! &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scripture.audio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;scripture.audio@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-do-you-do-this&#34;&gt;Why do you do this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s fun!  This started as a way to teach my own kids the Psalms in a radically efficient, engaging way.  It was enjoyable and so effective I started looking for an opportunity to share tracks with others.  Recording, performance and composition are skills I can apply to helping the church; I hope to give opportunity to more semi-professional or amateur musicians who want to serve the body of Christ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-m-curious-about-your-studio-what-do-you-use-to-make-recordings&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m curious about your studio.  What do you use to make recordings?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ears make records, not equipment.  But I enjoy using KRK monitors.  Microphones are from Neumann, DPA, Beyerdynamic and custom active ribbon microphones from Mark Fouxman of Samar Audio in Salt Lake City (VL37a serial #77 and #78).  Preamplification and A/D/A bit wrangling is by Audient (UK) and AppSys Pro Audio (Switzerland).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/2015/04/03/contact/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To drop a line, please email at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:scriptureaudio@gmail.com&#34;&gt;ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am active on Instagram at ScriptureAudio2017.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>