<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-139-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 139, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/348270651&amp;amp;color=%23ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;show_teaser=true&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Version 2, Upload date 10/23/17
**Download an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/bdraz99ziheg1zm/SA1701d_V2.mp3?dl=0&#34;&gt;MP3 of Psalm 139, Version 1 here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to part II of memorizing Psalm 139!  We got a little more time to listen to this long passage this month, with the full narration!  If you&amp;rsquo;ve stuck with us this far, congratulations; to review, we&amp;rsquo;ve memorized (1) Psalm every other month since June of this year, which puts some of us on track to stashing away more Scripture this year than in any recent years - especially if the Psalms hasn&amp;rsquo;t often been at the top of your list of texts to study!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the next week, ask each member of the family to follow along with the narrator and say as much of the Psalm as they can. This will heighten their awareness of which verses to focus their attention on, and putting one child on the spot slightly will actually focus the attention of all the others. I have two children, and we listen to the track four times, so each of the kids gets two cracks each at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we’re finding is that we do pretty well at the first half, but toward the end our memories get hazy! So be prepared to prompt them with a cheerful, “What comes next?” as the track goes on. The goal is for us all to know the beginning of each line and speak it before the narrator does. A little nudge here helps. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a large family, I don’t recommend pairing kids up - better for them to wait until tomorrow to try reciting along with the track, and only have one person go at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HOLIDAY NOTE ~~
After you hang in until Nov 1, when we take a break for the holidays, be looking forward to a chance to get your own full set of memorization tracks, and the full music soundtrack, on CD with a bonus of Psalm 23 for your little ones!  All profits will go to benefit the Heritage Church Building Fund, so keep this at the top of your Christmas present &amp;ldquo;to-buy&amp;rdquo; list for friends and family, or for your own family use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great week.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any experiences or tips to share about using this track?  Please share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>