<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-139-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 139, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/344999336&amp;amp;color=%23ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Version 1, Upload date 10/2/17
**Download an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/uj0462oq8phhsk1/SA1701d_V1.mp3?dl=0&#34;&gt;MP3 of Psalm 139, Version 1 here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good morning Heritage, and welcome to October!  We&amp;rsquo;ve been memorizing a Psalm bimonthly since June, and this will be our last month together before the holiday season begins in earnest.  As a bonus for sticking with us through Psalm 15, Psalm 103 and now Psalm 139, we&amp;rsquo;ll be emailing you a separation memorization set for Psalm 23 to use with your young &amp;lsquo;uns, at the end of the month!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month&amp;rsquo;s setting of Psalm 139 is JS Bach&amp;rsquo;s  Andante from the Sonata for Violin Solo in A minor, transcribed for the piano by the Alexander Siloti and performed by Christy Stouffer.  Thanks to Christy for her interpretation of this pensive piece, recorded at the end of a very long and exhausting day for her directing choral and ensemble numbers!  Thanks once again to Scott Young for providing the voiceover.
Here is the link to the page you&amp;rsquo;ll visit every day this month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re using a phone or tablet, you may want to copy-paste the address of this page directly onto your home screen.  It will create an icon, like an app, which will take you directly to the site with no fussing around every day to find your way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instructions:  Simple - gather the family and listen about 3 times in a row every day.  That&amp;rsquo;s it.  Try to find a time where things are fairly calm, when everyone is settled down and able to listen with relative attention.  The goal is not to be able to recite the Psalm this week - it&amp;rsquo;s to absorb the text through familiarity with the music, like soaking in a nice, hot bathtub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, do it again.  Easy, right?  You&amp;rsquo;ll hear from me again in about a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day.  Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any experiences or tips to share about using this track?  Please share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>