<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-103-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 103, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/326952134&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Upload date 6/7/17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the second week of memorizing Psalm 103, KJV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week, ask each member of the family to follow along with the narrator and say as much of the Psalm as they can.  This will heighten their awareness of which verses to focus their attention on, and putting one child on the spot slightly will actually focus the attention of all the others.  I have two children, and we listen to the track four times, so each of the kids gets two cracks each at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we&amp;rsquo;re finding is that we do pretty well at the first half, but toward the end our memories get hazy!  So be prepared to prompt them with a cheerful, &amp;ldquo;What comes next?&amp;rdquo; as the track goes on.  The goal is for us all to know the beginning of each line and speak it &lt;em&gt;before the narrator does&lt;/em&gt;.  A little nudge here helps.  :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a large family, I don&amp;rsquo;t recommend pairing kids up - better for them to wait until tomorrow to try reciting along with the track, and only have one person go at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find that a slightly different approach works for you?  Share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>