<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-103-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 103, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/329652726&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Upload date 6/23/17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Version 4&amp;rsquo; of Psalm 103 is ready for your final week of memorization.  A little more narration was removed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we round the bend and enter the home stretch, you have several homework assignments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each adult should pick out a standout verse to write on the family whiteboard, cork board, Sticky Note zone, or whatever you use to keep notes in view.  Stick it on your bathroom mirror.  Then start to find a use for that verse in conversation with your family, with friends, or when you send an email.  Whatever stands out to you personally about that verse, will be the very thing that&amp;rsquo;ll jog your elbow to make use of it, when the time is right.  Isn&amp;rsquo;t it a small victory, if out of every Psalm you knew, you had one key verse always at your fingertips?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start reciting as a family by switching off phrases.  I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put an example video on Instagram, but it&amp;rsquo;s simple to explain and fun to do!  Obviously the psalm is broken up into sentences or discrete thoughts.  As the track is playing, Dad or Mom should point to a different kid at random to say the next sentence.  The goal is to anticipate the beginning of the sentence such that we say the first words before Scott does on the track.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep practicing using a bit of Psalm 103 in your family prayers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any experiences or tips to share about using this track?  Please share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>