<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project-rsses on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Church CPC </title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/project/heritage/heritage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;psalm-139-kjv&#34;&gt;Psalm 139, KJV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; src=&#34;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/354073943&amp;amp;color=%23ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;show_teaser=true&amp;amp;visual=true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Version 3, Upload date 11/10/17
**Download an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/vwk0sd1x55g3sk9/SA1701d_V3.mp3?dl=0&#34;&gt;MP3 of Psalm 139, Version 3 here.&lt;/a&gt;
**Download an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/s/1felmxg9vsxip94/SA1701d_V4.mp3?dl=0&#34;&gt;MP3 of Psalm 139, Music Only here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So with this final Version 3 of Psalm 139, this concludes our 6 months of memorizing Psalms 15, 103 and 139!  &lt;a href=&#34;https://soundcloud.com/user-130139987/psalm-139-kjv-v4&#34;&gt;A music-only Version 4 to enjoy is linked here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a thank-you for sticking with us, I&amp;rsquo;d like to offer you all &lt;a href=&#34;https://soundcloud.com/user-130139987/sets/psalm-23-kjv&#34;&gt;a full set of memorization tracks of Psalm 23&lt;/a&gt;, set to Felix Mendelssohn&amp;rsquo;s Piano Trio #1 in D Major, 2nd mv&amp;rsquo;t, for your little ones who&amp;rsquo;ve not yet learned .  There are only three versions of this psalm, since it&amp;rsquo;s rather simple, but please enjoy the tracks and share with others if you like!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be making these memorization tracks, as well as the entirety of the recording project from March, available as a CD for purchase, so please keep an eye out.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing that the convenience of a CD might make memorization easier so if internet access or confusing instructions have been a problem, perhaps a CD will be a benefit to you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned back in June, this was a test project to gauge the level of your interest and enthusiasm for a method of learning Scripture that has benefited my family.  If you have comments or suggestions, please pass it along at scriptureaudio@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks again to Scott and the Centerville String Quartet for their efforts helping with this project, they&amp;rsquo;ve been great to work with.  I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of fun and looking forward to doing this again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jonathon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any experiences or tips to share about using this track?  Please share in the comments down below!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>