<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Scripture Audio</title>
    <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Scripture Audio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Purpose Scripture Audio is dedicated to helping churches, families and individuals absorb the Word of God through the enriching power of classical music. We believe in the power of music to enable Christians to deeply drink of the meaning of Scripture, to grow in their faith, teach their children, share their gifts, remember the past, and encourage each other. Our secondary goal is to bring amateur musicians back into service to the believing community by arranging local, on-the-ground recording sessions, joining both the production and consumption of music and Scripture narration in an enjoyable, lasting, and localized process of culture building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scriptureaudio.github.io/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Based out of Southwest Virginia, our focus is on church communities, home school groups and Christian schools in the Central &amp;amp; Southeast US. If you would like to inquire regarding a S/A production for your church or school group, or if you&amp;rsquo;d just like to drop us a line, please email us at ScriptureAudio@gmail.com.
Also check us out on Facebook and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>